Mikoy loves dramas,
and even I'm starting to like it too.
But what I don't like, is they
always incorporate a third-party.
Not now, I'm busy with the bakery.
This won't take long, I promise.
Angelito, I want to court Sofie.
Can you help me?
Report to me once you found them.
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my goodness, yes!
Alex burned her eggs!
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my goodness, yes!
Alex burned her eggs!
She's fearless against criminals
But she's no match for an egg
I wonder who's on Alex's mind?
I wonder who's in Alex's heart?
I know who Alex likes
You talk too much.
Hey!
Wait.
Is this the radioactive bomb?
Or maybe a weapon of mass destruction?
Okay, sorry.
What?
Did you cook this?
You know, I'm not forcing you to eat it.
Don't eat it, then. I'll eat it myself.
Look at you, getting offended already.
Of course we're going to try it.
PINAGPALA - SPECIAL BAKESHOP
Sofie.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
So you're a morning person too, huh?
No, I just came here early.
Where's Luisa?
Aren't you staying at the same hotel?
She said she'll follow later.
Are you staying nearby?
Yes. Actually, it's near the exit.
Just go straight and turn right.
-That's it.
-I see…
Want to go for a run?
Oh, sorry. I'm just not really
in the mood to run right now.
Besides, I told Mama Tess that
I'd help her with the cooking.
I actually have something cooking there.
Maybe next time.
All right, next time.
-You said it.
-Mmm…
I'll hold you to that.
You know, you two…
It's like you got a free honeymoon, huh?
It's like you're just on
a staycation here, right?
You single people, honestly.
The moment you see some sweetness,
you immediately get allergic to it.
Just let Chiara and me enjoy this.
You know,
we got exhausted working
our bones off in Hong Kong.
Why is this so hard?
To be fair, that was your decision.
Who told you to run away
and go to Hong Kong?
All right, it was our fault.
Come on, I just wanted to share
my realizations from that trip.
-All right then, share them.
-Never mind.
-Come on, go ahead!
-No way!
-Come on, come on.
-Okay, fine.
Of course, our work
at the restaurant was exhausting too.
-See? That's why.
-We'd wake up early,
then go to the market.
We'd carry supplies around
and prepare the ingredients.
It was hard.
Yes, that really was hard!
That's why, you know, part of me
actually missed being a COO.
Just sitting in an air-conditioned office.
-Giving people orders.
-What a life!
Yes, instead of doing manual labor, right?
But their job is to make sure
that people in the company have jobs.
I know that.
And what I'm sharing
isn't meant to compare
which job is harder.
My point is, at the end of the day,
there's also satisfaction
in restaurant work.
In manual labor.
Because there,
everyone listens and everyone helps.
And you create something
with your hands, right?
That's amazing.
Then you see how happy people are
eating the food you cooked.
They appreciate it,
and that feels really good.
Wow, these eggs are delicious!
You want some? Fine, I'll eat them all.
Amazing!
I absolutely love the crispy bits!
No, they're completely burnt,
Crunching it down
Crunch, crunch, so delicious!
That's right, bro!
Okay, bro!
-See that!
-Okay!
-That's how it is!
-There you go!
So if I had to choose,
I'd really prefer a job like that.
One that's not in an office.
Because when you're in an office,
you rarely get to see
the people you're making happy.
And sooner or later,
that sense of fulfillment
starts to fade from your heart, right?
But I'd rather be sad in a huge mansion,
wearing my Rolex.
And then,
I'd have lots of money.
It's hard being broke.
You suddenly find yourself crying,
when you have no money.
So what now?
Looks like this is hopeless.
Maybe I should just move on.
You could.
Wow, really?
Not even a few words of encouragement?
So that's what you wanted to hear.
You should've said so right away.
Instead of acting all sad over there,
like you're ready to give up on Sofie.
Of course I'll support you.
But if
you're not even sure about Sofie yet,
then maybe it's better
if you just give up.
You have a point.
But how about this? Favor.
Maybe you can help me find out
Sofie's favorites, like her
favorite color, favorite food.
Anything that could help me court her.
All right, I'll do it for you.
You really love me.
Give me a hug.
Hey, wait. Is that a helicopter?
Looks like one of you escaped.
What? I'm heading out first.
Hey!
-Go ahead.
-You might be with…
PINAGPALA
SPECIAL BAKESHOP
Hello?
How are you doing?
How's our houdini couple there?
Did they do another new stunt?
Surprisingly none.
They're just making
the safehouse their staycation.
But nothing alarming.
And Cocoy is just monitoring
the money flow of the Vertex.
How about you, Bok?
Are you okay?
Aside from cooking, I haven't really
faced any other challenges.
So you've already shown them
your cooking skills.
Sianong, just get to the point.
Why did you call?
Is there a problem at the agency?
Here?
No.
Everything's fine here, okay?
I just wanted to remind you
that you need to send an update.
ASAP, because Senator Quintin
will be briefing
the President.
All right, I'll send it once I'm done.
Agent Alex, we have a problem!
What?
What's the problem? Is it the enemy?
-Take cover! Take cover!
-No.
There's no water!
What? That's it?
What do you mean, that's it?
How am I supposed to finish
washing these dishes?
I can go outside and look for
a place to buy water.
No one is leaving.
This place is in a secluded area.
If it's not an ice cream vendor
who spots you,
it'll be a taho vendor.
What's our game plan?
We can't be without water.
I haven't even showered. I stink already!
And I also need to freshen up.
What's that?
That can only mean one thing.
There's movement in their crypto wallet.
See?! I knew it.
They're using Vertex
to move funds into crypto.
Looks like they routed it through a bank.
How did they manage that?
Shouldn't that have been flagged?
Fifty million pesos?
Not if it's a corporate account
under a legitimate business,
which is Vertex.
They're making it look like
operational expenses,
or business expenses through
multiple transactions.
It's only ordinary people
who get scrutinized by banks here.
That's not all. Look at this.
They're using crypto to transfer
the same amount.
I checked the satellite mapping,
and it's an isolated area in Tanay.
It's possible that this is
the new operational site
of La Morte Bianca in the Philippines.
You're right, Cocoy.
I'm sure their place will
be heavily guarded.
Self-contained and
almost impossible to infiltrate.
Like a mafia village in Prague and Sicily.
Do you think
they're still looking for the bomb?
Or have they already found it?
Well, that's the question
we need answered.
Because if they already have the bomb,
it means catastrophe is near.
And if they don't,
then we still have time to stop them.
Mr. President.
And it did not pass through
standard banking channels.
And she used Vertex,
owned by the Valtrovis,
as a front.
To convert cryptocurrency
into Philippine pesos.
They're the ones
we've been watching for years.
The Concordat.
Their goal is to establish
an administration here in the Philippines,
and spread their terror from here.
In fact, they immediately found the site
that Isabella purchased
as their stronghold.
Impressive, Senator Quintin.
Even your barong is impressive!
You could run for higher office.
Oh, Mr. President.
I still have to
eat a lot of rice and chips.
Although, I don't like
chips because I'm allergic to that.
That was a nuclear bomb!
There.
-Bechay, get this.
-Here, thank you very much.
Come back, okay?
Promise?
Just a typical Angelito…
-Come here, look at them.
-Oh, my. Look at this.
What do you think? What if…
there comes a chance where
Angelito has to choose.
Who do you think he would choose?
They're both kind.
They're both beautiful too.
True that.
But if you ask me?
I'm Team Luisa Mae, Team AngeLu.
Because look,
Luisa Mae seems good with people,
she adjusts to others.
And with Sofie…
She always has to be the one in control.
That's not really okay
all the time, right?
She's just a kid!
She takes after her father!
But me, you know?
If you ask me?
I'm Team SofieLito.
Because of vibes.
Vibes? What vibes?
Just vibes, that's what it is.
That only a mother like me can feel.
After everything you said
it's just "vibes"?
I'm Team Sofie!
Sofie.
Guys.
I'm so sticky!
Still no water?
My brain is getting fried looking
for La Morte Bianca.
I feel like I want to drink
the water dripping from the AC.
Hello Agent Dara.
When will there be water?
Since the safe house
is in a remote location,
you'll probably get
your water ration tomorrow.
They prioritize areas that are closer.
So by that time,
you might finally get water.
So there's no point
sending them there tomorrow.
Wait, what happened?
Why is there no water supply?
A water pipeline was damaged.
They said water might come back
tonight, around 9 p.m.
Is there any other way?
There's a hand pump near the safe house,
around 700 meters away.
Can you walk that far?
I don't have a choice.
Okay, bye.
We need to fetch water.
Mikoy, come with me.
Okay, I'll come with you and Chiara.
I'll just stay here, I'm too sticky.
You two go with Agent Alex.
After all,
you're just going to fetch water, right?
If Chiara stays here,
Cocoy needs to stay here too.
-Let's go, Mikoy.
-Okay.
-Hurry up, sweetheart.
-Take care, you two.
All right.
This is hot.
What is it? Do you want to say something?
My favorite color is blue, what about you?
What?
Where did that come from?
I like pink.
Mine depends on my mood.
But today, red.
I like yellow.
Sunshine yellow or mustard yellow?
Okay.
What's your favorite dish?
Pork sinigang ribs,
-With taro.
-With taro!
Morning would work too!
For men?
What do you like?
I like someone a bit tall.
But not too short either.
Personality?
Simple.
Kind-hearted.
And also,
down to earth.
So you like earthworms?
Just stand it up and it's fine.
Perfect height.
And living down to earth.
Right?
Exactly, Bechay!
-You're so good, you're so good!
-Oh, you…
Because, you know, he really does
look like a checkered earthworm,
just smarter.
Wait, what are you guys
even talking about?
Just Sofie's favorites.
Wait, it's almost done.
Movie? What's your favorite movie?
Wait, wait, wait.
I know what you're doing.
This is slambook questions, right?
Yes.
I saw it on the internet.
For whom?
For you or for someone else?
So full of herself!
Hey Mikoy, you're wasting water.
Sorry.
Feels like military training, huh?
Isn't this how it is?
Look at that, you spilled it.
Come on.
I'm cutting your water ration.
How dare you! Take that back.
No, final decision.
Final?
Really final?
-You're playing now?
-Is that the final?
-What?
-Enough.
-All right, so?
-Oh, you're attacking too.
Hey!
Are you seriously
going to play with water?
Hey! Mikoy, stop it.
Seriously, seriously.
-Okay I will use this—
-Go on, try it.
-Go ahead.
-Okay, stop it, stop it.
-Go on.
-Don't waste water like that.
Wasting?
Yes, it's so far away!
Look, I'm carrying two, you just have one.
Of course, I'm a girl, what do you expect?
Fine! Wait.
-Enough, stop it.
-What is this?
It's like… it's raining a bit.
-Mikoy, what.
-It's drizzling?
-So annoying.
-It's raining!
Hey, what is it?
You're so annoying.
-Really?
-Oh, you want it?
-No, I'm just saying.
-Fine.
Want some jelly beans?
I found some in the pantry, want some?
Okay, what a shame.
Guys! We've got jelly!
Hey, I want some!
This jelly is so good! So jelly!
Wakes you up! So jelly!
If you were really listening
to my answers earlier.
What's my favorite dish?
That's it?
Pork sinigang ribs, with taro.
Even in the morning.
Nice, nice, nice, okay, okay.
Here.
What's my favorite color?
Yellow!
And not just any yellow,
sunflower yellow.
See?
Nice!
Here, here.
What's my favorite flower?
I didn't even ask that!
You're not listening.
But that's easy.
What?
Sunflower!
You got it right!
But I feel like you won't get this one.
Yes.
What's my favorite song?
The one you always sing.
What?
There.
In love, huh.
So you're in love.
Is this the house?
Yes it seems like this is it.
Oh, there's someone.
Sir.
Are you from here?
Why?
We're just here to do a census.
Do you live in this house?
Census? Isn't that every five years?
We already had a census last year.
-Let's go, let's go.
-You're new here.
You know that's dehydrating, but okay!
-Okay.
-Later.
-You go ahead.
-Okay.
Okay.
Welcome to the criminal TED Talk.
So here's what happened,
I checked their crypto,
one source only,
but all their money was there.
It was sent to
a Taytay residence, very secured.
The're so many— Lots of guards.
But I got it with my app.
So there. Do you understand?
Anyway,
at this point, we still don't know
why La Morte Bianca is building a site.
That's it!
-Yes.
-Got it!
-Nice!
-Not confirmed yet.
Well.
Or if you really want to know,
what they know,
we need to talk to one of their people.
Mikoy in our line of work,
it's hard to trust someone.
Because if we fail, there are people
that will be hurt and endangered.
I won't promise
that I will give her my trust.
But I will try to.
Thank you.
Sir, we have a proposal.
Chiara wants to reconnect
with Viktor Valtrovi
-to get information—
-No!